floraindia.com 2011-05-11

# Send Privacy Policy India - FloraIndia.com - Online Florist - Flowers, Cakes and Sweets Delivery Service

**FloraIndia.com** , recognizes and respects the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers, registered members ("Members") and users, and has established this Privacy Policy as a result. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of:

  * the personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web site, respond to our emails, place orders via mail or fax, or otherwise contact us via telephone, email, fax or mail, 
  * why we gather information from you, 
  * how we collect it, 
  * how we use it, and 
  * the choices you have regarding our use of personal information you have provided. 

Note: You must be 18 years or older to use, subscribe or register as a member of FloraIndia.com. The Web Site is a general audience site and we do not knowingly collect, maintain or disclose personal information from or about children.

**Why do we gather information?**

FloraIndia.com gathers personal information to help improve our products and customer service, to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you, and your gift and message recipients, of special offers and discounts from us.

**What information do we gather?**

We collect information through our Web Site, emails, and telephone. We collect some or all of the following types of information:

  * your name, address, telephone number, email address, 
  * billing information on our secure payment gateway (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), 
  * products purchased and occasion type (for example, Mother's Day), 
  * any promotion code and related information, 
  * Message and gift recipients' names, addresses and telephone numbers, and 
  * other information you provide to us. 

Information you provide to us may be collected by us even if an order, registration, or other process is started but not completed or otherwise cancelled. Members may also add to their Address Book the name, address and telephone number of friends or other persons to whom they may wish to send gifts or expressions. Only Members have the right to view and edit their Address Book entries.

**How we use "Cookies" and "Action Tags".**

A "cookie" is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, user or Member and to provide certain features to you. Most web browsers allow you to instruct the browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of the FloraIndia.com Web Site, such as the shopping cart, may not function properly.

Our Web Site also uses a common web technology "called "action tags" (also called single pixel gifs or web beacons) to anonymously track purchase, usage and other web activity information. Action tags (including third party tags) may be used to provide data to third parties for tracking purposes. However, our Web Site does not use action tags to collect or transfer personal information.

**How we use the information we collect**

We use information we collect to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience, to inform you and your gift and message recipients of offers and discounts from FloraIndia.com.

We may combine information we receive from you via our Web Site, emails and telephone with information from our Affiliates and third parties. We use the combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us and to communicate with you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to disclose information you provide to us as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests and as necessary or appropriate, in our view, to operate the Web Site, process orders or registrations, to conduct promotions, and to protect the rights or property of the Company, its Affiliates, users, customers, recipients, Members, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants and Associates.

**Consent to Transfer and Submission**

FloraIndia.com is operated in India. If you are located outside India, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to India. By using the Web Site or otherwise providing us with information, you hereby consent to this transfer.

In addition, if you submit data to us about other individuals (such as your message and gift recipients), you agree that you have obtained consent from each such individual to the submission, transfer and processing of the information. Although personal information collected by us through the Web Site, emails, and telephone is used by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in India may not be as stringent as those in other countries.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

FloraIndia.com wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to affiliated or third-party web sites, you will be subject to the privacy policies and terms of use of those web sites, not ours. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms whenever using, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other web site.

**Security and Passwords**

If you place an order on our Web site, it encrypts the credit card number you submit prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. This technology works best when the Web Site is viewed using Microsoft's Internet Explorer®, Mozilla Firefox® or Google Chrome®. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard personal information once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information we receive.

Portions of the Web Site (such as our Member registration and Address Book) may require registration and log-in processes in which you will select a user ID and password (collectively, the "Password"). Passwords provided to you by us are the confidential property of the Company and may be used by you solely for your individual use of the Web Site (and otherwise as specified by us). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Password and for all activities that occur using your Password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your Password or accounts.

**Corrections**

If you would like to update or correct information previously provided to us, please send an e-mail with your new information, including your complete name, postal address, and email address to serve@floraindia.com.

Members can modify and update their membership information (including name, mailing address, telephone number and email address) by accessing the password-protected "Edit Personal Info" page.

**Your Consent and Changes to this Policy**

Subject to the above provisions, by using our Web Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, of which this policy is a part. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time as new features or services are added, suggestions from our customers are incorporated or other changes are made. We will post the revised Privacy Policy on our Web Site at least 30 days prior to their effective date - unless we believe changes must take effect sooner to comply with law or to protect the Company or our customers, users, Members, recipients, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants, Associates and Affiliates, in which case the changes will be effective upon posting or as otherwise specified.

In addition, if you would like notice of changes to the Privacy Policy or Terms of Use prior to their taking effect (or upon taking effect, if effective immediately), email us at serve@floraindia.com from the email address to which you would like notice sent. By using FloraIndia.com, after such changes take effect, you agree to be legally bound and to abide by the revised Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, of which this policy is a part.

**Your Comments**

FloraIndia.com welcomes feedback concerning this Privacy Policy. Please send your comments and questions to serve@floraindia.com.   
  
Please note delivery confirmation email of all Mother's Day orders will be sent on 9th May due to heavy rush of Mother's Day orders.

_Forthcoming Occasions:_ **Father's Day** : 19 Jun    **Cheer Up Day** : 11 Jul   

Save on your purchase by making a combo of your choice. Click here to know  
about **Combo Price** and **AutoCombo** _!_  
  
| **Power Points** |  | **Testimonials** |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  **All** major credit cards accepted.  
**Verisign** secure payment gateway.  
**Free Shipping** in 300 cities in India.  
Fresh Flowers are **Hand Delivered**.  
**No** extra or hidden **charges**.  
Orders for **Sunday and Holiday also accepted** , at no extra charges.  
**Same day delivery** in all major towns and cities of India.  
**Hand picked** fresh indian and exotic flowers at the best prices.  
|  |  I must admit I was quite hesitant when ordering from you because I have never ordered anything online before and didnt know what to expect. But I have to say you people really got it right! Right from my custom ordered cheesecake (which I heard was quite yummy!) to the flowers, everything that was delivered was exactly what I had asked for and exactly what was promised. Also the gift was delivered exactly on time, and your prices are also reasonable enough. My gift was a huge success thanks to you! I'll definitely order from you again, and recommend you to my friends as well. 

**Dr.Sonali Sud, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi**  
  
**Send Fresh Flowers, Cakes and Sweets to India. Quality delivery network all over India.**
